《威尔和格蕾丝》是在摄影棚观众前现场录制的
"Will & Grace" Is recorded in front of a live studio audience.
你非要走这么慢吗
Do you have to go so slow?
我这是谨慎起见  货物很珍贵
I'm being careful. Precious cargo.
就是颗西瓜而已
It's a watermelon.
我才不会用真的宝宝来测试婴儿车
I'm not gonna test out a new stroller with an actual baby.
我又不是疯子
I'm not a crazy person.
你觉得她穿得够多了吗
Do you think she's dressed warm enough?
怎么闪闪发亮
Why is it shiny?
我的天
Oh, my God.
你在西瓜上抹了防晒霜吗
Did you put sunscreen on that watermelon?
防止什么  西瓜瘤吗[黑素瘤]
To prevent what? Melon-noma?
你自从见过那个婴儿防护员后  就变成了怪人
You've been a wack-a-doo ever since you met with that baby proofer.
奥伊先生让一切都变得真实起来
Mr. Ow-ie made everything very real,
你生气不过是因为
and you're just mad because
我对零食抽屉做了防护措施
I baby proofed the snack drawer
你不得不用嘴咬开
and you had to bite it open.
你也要有小孩了  你怎么不害怕
You're having a baby, too. Why aren't you terrified?
我怕啊  怕你
I am terrified, of you.
你怎么就不能像正常人一样通过吃来缓解情绪
Why don't you eat your feelings like normal people?
放松  淡定
Just relax. Calm down.
我很淡定  我很放松
I am calm. I am relaxed.
快救我离开这死亡陷阱
Get me off of this death trap!
不不  你按的是詹姆斯那层楼
No, no, no! You pressed James's floor!
詹姆斯
James?
就是你睡了他儿子的那人
Oh, the guy you slept with his son?
好了  我们不用回顾这件事
Okay, we don't have to revisit the whole thing--
-以及他老子  -够了
- And his father? - Okay, that's enough.
你还在他家拉了一大堆屎  毁了他的公寓
And--and you took such a massive dump, it destroyed his apartment?
我的痛苦和尴尬
My pain and embarrassment
不应该给你带来这么多欢乐
should not bring you so much amusement.
然而  就是让我欢乐
And yet, it does.
格蕾丝  他现在恰好在走廊里的几率能有多高
Grace, what are the odds he's gonna be in the hallway right now?
事实证明  相当高
Turns out, pretty good.
你好  格蕾丝
Hello, Grace.
你好  詹姆斯
Hi, James.
「西瓜妮」和我走楼梯好了
Uh, Melon-ie and I are gonna take the stairs.
威尔和格蕾丝
第11季  第11集
工作怎么样
So, how's work?
挺好的
It's good.
那就好
Good.
我看到报纸说
Oh, I read about that new dolphin
你们的海洋馆里引入了一头新海豚
that you guys have at the-at the aquarium.
实际上是鼠海豚
It's a porpoise, actually.
我一直想要和海豚共游
I have always wanted to swim with a dolphin.
再说一次  是鼠海豚
Again, porpoise.
不幸的是  不对公众开放
Uh, unfortunately, it's closed to the public,
但或许我可以破例一次
but I guess I could make an exception.
为你
For you.
真的吗
Really?
你不记恨我对你做的那些事吗
After everything I've done to you?
不如这么看吧
Let's look at it this way.
你没法做出比那些更可怕的事了
You can't do anything worse.
威尔  早午餐  快点
Will, brunch! Hurry up!
我不能让我血液中的酒精浓度降到太低
I can't let my blood alcohol level get too low,
不然我会意识到我的朋友们很无趣
or I'll realize my friends are boring.
再做一次应急演练
Just one more emergency drill.
-杰克  你在计时吗  -在呢
- Jack, are you timing me? - On it.
预备  各就各位  鬼知道说什么
On your mark, get set-- Whatever.
好  这次是地震
Okay, this time it's an earthquake.
虽然在曼哈顿很罕见  不过也不是不可能
Rare in Manhattan, but not impossible.
杰克  把它当成真婴儿抱着
Jack, hold it like it's a baby,
而不是一个喜欢打扮成婴儿的成年人
not like it's an adult man who likes to dress like a baby.
你爸靠毒舌抨击别人
Your daddy lashes out
这样他就不需要自我反省了
so he doesn't have to work on himself.
不  他需要的
Yes, he does.
稳稳把这个盘绕在身上  拿上奶粉
Just wrap this securely, grab some formula,
然后安全带你离开大楼
and then get you safely out of the building.
现在水果成了蔬菜了[植物人]
And the fruit is now a vegetable.
这"小宝贝"味道真不错
That's good baby.
我要怎么熬过去
How am I ever gonna get through this?
外面有太多可怕的事情
There's--there's so many terrible things out there
我得保护这孩子不被伤害
I have to protect this baby from.
那些当父母的晚上怎么能睡得着啊
How does any parent sleep at night?
靠酒和安眠药
Alcohol and sleeping pills.
但是  这条很重要
But--and this is important--
你必须两者一起服用
you have to take them together.
好吧  亲爱的
Okay, dear.
我就知道会有这么一天
I knew this was coming.
我们得让你放松下来
We have got to get you to relax.
我能从你脸上看出来
I can read it all over your face
因为你的压力粉刺就像盲文一样
because your stress pimples are like Braille.
不要  再吃
No... more...
乳制品  好了  快走
Dairy. Yeah, come on.
我们走
Let's go.
我知道一个好地方  快
I know just the place. Come on.
好吧
Okay, fine.
等不及想看看你们
Can't wait to see what filthy,
要带我去什么下流堕落的鬼地方
depraved hellhole you're taking me to.
只要那地方有变装皇后
As long as there's a drag queen
由她来主持宾果游戏  我就满足了
calling out bingo numbers, I'm happy.
然后呢
So, what?
这里等下会变迪厅吗
This turns into a disco later,
还是说我们得走到里面
or do we have to pass through the back
才能进到真正的夜总会
to get to the real club?
不是啦  就这儿
No, this is it.
这是我的教堂
This is my church.
什么
What?
你去教堂的吗
You go to church?
每周日上午
Every Sunday morning.
锤哥  甜茶  老吉  小乔  男神们庇佑我
Hemsworth, Chalamet, Gyllenhaal, Jonas.
你总是跟我说
You always tell me
你每周日上午要和你妈待在一起
you're spending time with your mom on Sunday mornings.
是啊  我们都来这里
Yeah, this is where we go,
我们每次都迟到一小时
and we're always an hour late
因为她总是不知道该戴哪顶帽子
because she can't find the right hat.
这是教堂  不是赛马比赛   朱迪丝
It's a church, not the Kentucky Derby, Judith.
好吧  我不知道你们为什么带我来这
Well, I don't know why you brought me here,
但我要去尿尿
but I have to tinkle.
是时候化酒为水了
Time to turn the wine into water.
耶稣曾化水为酒
这种人祷告  上帝不会理的
Well, those prayers ain't getting answered.
看看这大蛙鞋[浪荡女]
Wow, look at those big flippers.
这还是第一次有男人
That's the first time a man's said that to me
在我穿着蛙鞋的时候这样说我
when I was actually wearing flippers.
你看起来可爱极了
Well, you look adorable.
其实  我刚刚在想
You know, I was thinking,
等下要不要一起吃个晚饭呢
maybe we could grab dinner later?
前提是你乐意再给我们一次机会
I mean, if you're interested in giving us another try.
简短点的回答是
The short answer is
我不敢相信你居然这么宽宏大量
I can't believe how forgiving you are.
或许有点宽宏过头了
Maybe too forgiving.
但是话说回来  能够原谅我犯下的错误
But then again, someone who could forgive my mistakes
或许是一个男人身上  我最需要的品质
might be the quality that I need most in a man,
所以  我愿意  我想再给我们一次机会
so, yes, I would love to give us another try.
这是简短的回答吗
That was the short answer?
这样吧  我去把装备穿上
Look, I'm gonna go get my gear on
之后你就可以去见努努了
and then you can meet Nook-Nook.
但严格意义上说
But technically,
你是不该出现在这里的
you're not supposed to be in here,
所以拜托你不要乱跑
so please do me a favor
在我回来前  不要越过黄线
and do not cross that yellow line until I get back.
遵命  长官
Yes, sir.
你在这儿啊
Oh, there you are!
看看这笑容
Look at that smile.
我要和你合影  来了哦
I'm gonna take a picture with you. Yes, I am.
不妙  不好看啊
Oh, no, that's not good.
是  是我的问题
It's...it's...it's me.
你没问题  你很好看
It's not you. You're good.
皮肤真好
Great skin.
笑一个
Now smile.
居然没厕纸
No toilet paper.
等等  连马桶都没有
Oh, hold on. No toilet.
好吧  看来要在这里面用第三世界的那一套了
Okay, looks like we're going all third world up in this thing.
天呐  我在摸海豚
Oh, my God! I'm petting a dolphin!
你喜欢那样吗
Oh, you like that?
想让我给你的肚子挠痒痒吗
Am I gonna tickle your belly?
要吗  那是你的肚脐眼吗
Huh? Is that your belly button?
哇  这肚脐眼可真大
Wow, that's a big belly button.
你真的很喜欢那样  对吧
Wow, you are really, really liking that, aren't you?
原来那玩意儿不是肚脐眼
That wasn't your belly button.
你好啊  伙计
Hey, buddy.
你那边有厕纸吗
You got any toilet paper in your stall?
没有
No.
那能不能帮我换点零钱[银行窗口]
How about two fives for a ten?
这里是告解室
This is a confessional.
如果你想找洗手间...
If you're looking for the bathroom...
不用  我没事
No, I'm good.
把憋回去就好了  等该释放的时候再释放
I can put the cork back in till it's time to party.
所以  这里面是怎么回事
So, what goes on in here?
人们来这里  是希望自己的罪得到赦免
People come here to be absolved of their sins.
那我想玩这游戏
Ooh, I wanna play.
那你就要先说
Then start by saying,
「原谅我  神父  我有罪」
"Forgive me, Father, for I have sinned."
-如果我没有罪呢  -你当然会有
- What if I haven't sinned? - Of course you have.
众生皆有罪
Everyone sins.
你肯定有辜负的人
Well, there must be someone you've wronged,
你违背的戒律
some commandment you've broken.
神父  「阴部瘙痒」只让我意识到
Padre, the only thing a burning bush ever told me
Burning Bush
在《圣经》里是"燃烧的荆棘"
赶紧用青霉素
was go get penicillin.
或许你可以说说撒谎的罪过
Well maybe then talk about the times you've lied.
或是偷盗  又或是背叛别人
Or, uh, stolen. Or betrayed another.
好吧
Okay.
我们得在这待上很久了
We're gonna be here for a while.
你想来点上帝的"婴儿爽身粉"吗
You in the mood for a little God's baby powder?
我还是很震惊  你居然会来教堂
I'm still in shock that you come here.
为什么  你知道我家信天主教的啊
Why? You know I grew up Catholic.
是没错  但我以前都不知道你如此虔诚
Yeah, but it's a hidden level I didn't know you had.
这就如同发现
It's--it's like discovering
充气儿童泳池有深水区一样
that an inflatable kiddie pool has a deep end.
由于我们此刻身处上帝的殿堂
'Cause we are in the Lord's house,
我不该拿我屁股里的"深水区"开玩笑
I shalt not make a joke about my deep end.
我喜欢这里
I like it here.
常让我想起我最喜欢的电影
Reminds me of my favorite movie.
我猜是《修女也疯狂》
Let me guess: "Sister Act."
才不是
No.
是《修女也疯狂2》
"Sister Act 2."
♪快乐的主  我们崇拜你♪
♪ Joyful, joyful Lord we adore thee ♪
♪荣耀的上帝  万主之主♪
♪ God of glory Lord of lords ♪
再说了
By the way,
觉得有人时刻在关照我  那种感觉真的很好
it's nice to feel like someone's always looking out for me, you know?
我就是很难去信奉一种看不到的东西
I just find it hard to believe in something you can't see.
如果我说
I mean, what--what if I said
有一只魔法兔子在控制着宇宙呢
there was a--a magic rabbit that controlled the universe?
你会说  "拿出证据"
You'd say, "Prove it."
我会说"我拿不出来"  对话就结束了
I'd say, "I can't." End of discussion.
听着  你有没有看过《海军罪案调查处》
Look. Have you ever seen "NCIS?"
没有
No.
你认识的人里有看过的吗
Has anyone you know ever seen it?
没有
No.
但你依然相信这剧是真实存在的
But you still believe it exists.
威尔  上帝就是《海军罪案调查处》
Will, God is "NCIS."
但是那些教徒"以教会名义"
What about all the bad stuff that's been done
对我们这种人做过那么多坏事
"in the name of the church" to people like you and me?
《圣经》里大概只提过三次同性恋
There's maybe three references in there to homosexuality
但叫大家不要吃贝类却有差不多12次
and, like, 12 about not eating shellfish,
也没见虔诚的盲从教徒抗议龙虾啊
but you don't see religious bigots picketing Red Lobster.
他们就是选了自己想相信的内容
So they pick and choose.
我们也可以选啊
We can pick and choose, too.
这就如同我们以前常去的那家第8大街的酒吧
It's like that bar we used to go to on 8th Street
那里放的音乐很烂  酒也兑了水
with the bad music and the watered-down drinks.
但那里的男人都超火辣
Oh, the guys there were so hot, though.
没错  所以我们还是一直去
Exactly, so we kept going back,
因为尽管那酒吧缺点多多
because despite the issues,
它依然有值得去的理由
it had something to offer.
所以上帝是《海军罪案调查处》
So God is "NCIS"
而《圣经》是毛皮酒吧吗
andthe Bible is the Rawhide?
你终于听明白了  孩子
You're catching on, my child.
-你准备好见努努了吗  -当然
- You ready to meet Nook-Nook? - You betcha.
你没越过黄线吧
You didn't cross the line, did you?
没有  什么界线都没越过
Nope. No lines were crossed.
它见到你真的很兴奋呢
Wow, she's really excited to meet you.
可能我很擅长"取悦"动物吧
I, uh, guess I just must have a way with animals.
下水前  我得跟你说些注意事项
Okay, before we get in, a few precautions.
努努处在发情期
Because she's mating,
所以它现在性欲高涨
right now Nook-Nook is in a highly sexualized state.
是啊  可不是嘛
Yeah, tell me about it.
我是说  对待它一定要万分小心
I mean, she needs to be handled very carefully.
绝不能做出任何会影响它交配的事
We can't do anything to disrupt the process.
假设她...自慰了
Hypothetically, would it disrupt the process
那会影响到它交配吗
if she were to, say, pleasure herself?
海豚又没有手  怎么自慰
Well, they don't have hands, so--
不过假如它真的做了
but, yeah. Hypothetically, I mean,
那的确会严重降低它交配的意愿
that would seriously upset her ability to mate,
那将是个惨剧
which would be a tragedy
因为这物种仅剩它这一条雌性了
because she's the last female of her species.
你们在全世界都找遍了吗
Have you looked everywhere?
当然了
Of course we have.
喂  好的
Hello? Oh, okay.
我马上过去
Um, I'll be right there.
是安保人员打来的
That was security.
他们想让我看一段监控录像
Some surveillance footage they want me to see.
这里有摄像头吗
There are cameras in here?
是的  每个角落都有
Oh, yeah. They're all over.
完了  走开  不行就是不行
Oh, my God. Hey, no means no.
你简直像是在...
It's almost like you're having a--
你这人有什么毛病啊
What is wrong with you?!
我在杂志上读到过她这种人
I've read about people like her.
-这是种癖好  -这才不是癖好
- It's a fetish. - It's not a fetish.
没错  他们认为这是爱呢
Oh, that's right. They think it's love.
好吧  我这次的确做得不对
Okay, okay, this is not my finest moment.
但我为自己辩解一下
But in my defense,
是它主动勾引我在先
she came on to me.
你自己变态还怪鱼
You're blaming the fish?
这是你做过的最恶劣的事
This is the worst thing you have ever done,
那就很能说明问题了
and that's saying a lot.
她就是那个拉了一泡巨大的...
Is she the one who took a giant cr--
没错  吉妮芙
Yes, Genevieve!
用了三个女仆才清理干净那摊血
It took three maids to clean up all that blood.
又用了两个管家除掉那三个女仆
And two butlers to get rid of the three maids.
但是最终  就好像这一切都没发生过
But in the end, it was like it never happened,
他当选了总统
and he got elected President.
而你并不认为这一切是有任何罪的
And you don't think any of that is sinful?
什么罪  无罪
What sin? No sin.
你才是有罪之人  假新闻
You're the sinner. Fake news.
稍等下
Oh, hold on.
我想着这可能要挺久
I thought this might take a while,
就点了些小点心
so I ordered a little snicky-snack.
斯密特
Smitty?
你好  沃克夫人
Hello, Mrs. Walker.
你现在开始当送餐小哥了吗
Oh, you're delivering Postmates?
你怎么没在「老国王科尔酒吧」工作了
What happened to your job at the Old King Cole Bar?
那不是个什么愉快的故事
It's--it's not a good story.
稍等下  拉比
Hang on to your yarmulke, Rabbi.
悲剧加斯密特等于喜剧
Tragedy plus Smitty equals comedy.
我当时不知道他们把酒吧外面的
Well, I--I didn't know that they had just waxed
那些大理石台阶打过蜡
the marble steps outside the bar.
提醒下  这事的结果虽是可预料的
Okay, you can see this one coming,
但你可以享受这过程
but you'll enjoy the ride.
医生说我的髋骨在第一层台阶时摔碎了
The doctors say that I shattered my hips on the first stair,
但是  等我滚到楼梯最下面时
but by the time I got to the bottom of the landing,
我更像是一块块的拼图玩具  而不是人类
well, I was more jigsaw puzzle than man.
别急着笑  他还能更出彩
Hold on. He's gonna top it.
或许你注意到我比之前矮了几英寸
Well, maybe you noticed that I was a few inches shorter,
那是因为我的骨盆被整个取出了
and--and--and that's because my pelvis is gone.
我也没有膝盖供孙儿们坐在上面了
I--I have no lap for my great grandchildren to sit on.
这才是点睛之笔
And there it is.
斯密特
Ah, Smitty.
五星好评
Five stars.
你不觉得嘲笑别人的不幸是有罪的吗
Don't you think laughing at another soul's misfortune is sinful?
什么  才不是
What? No.
那是我们之间的相处方式  已经持续好多年了
That's our thing we've been doing for years.
他超爱的
He loves it.
你确定吗
Are you sure about that?
你问过他吗
Have you ever asked him?
-没有  -那你怎么知道的
- No. - Well then, how can you know?
恐怕我的确不知道
I guess I can't.
天呐
Um, gosh,
如果我这些年来一直在伤害斯密特
if I'd been hurting Smitty all these years,
那的确是一种罪
that would be a sin.
但愿我能赶上他
Oh, I hope I can catch him.
斯密特  斯密特  慢点
Smitty! Smitty, slow down!
没时间闲聊了  沃克夫人
No time to chat, Mrs. Walker.
我要在15分钟内赶到布鲁克林
I gotta be in Brooklyn in 15 minutes.
听我说  斯密特
Oh, uh, listen, Smitty.
我希望你别介意我有时候
I hope you don't mind that I sometimes
在听你的不幸遭遇时  忍不住发出笑声
let a giggle or two escape when you tell me about your adventures.
我完全不介意  谢谢你能这么问
Oh, not at all. It's nice of you to ask.
事实是
Um, truth is,
每当我遭遇这种不幸时
when those bad things happen to me,
我在心里总是想着
I always think to myself,
"这一定会让沃克夫人开怀大笑的"
"Mrs. Walker's gonna enjoy this."
很高兴知道这点  斯密特
Well, that's nice to know, Smitty,
但不管怎样
but all the same,
等你回到你的公寓时
when you get back to your apartment,
将会收到一张支票  以确保
there's going to be a check to make sure
你再也不用干送餐的苦差事了
that you never have to work for Postmates again.
但我爱这工作啊
But I--I love it,
这个代步车引无数美女竞脱裤呢
and--and this scooter is a real panty-dropper.
谢谢你  沃克夫人
Thank you, Mrs. Walker.
不客气  斯密特
You're welcome, Smitty.
对了  斯密特
Oh, and, um, Smitty?
就此别过  笑林再见
See you in the funny papers.
瞧瞧这闪闪发亮的楼梯啊
Look at those shiny stairs.
你非得当笑到最后的那个人
You always have to get the last laugh,
是吧  你个笑星[屁股]
don't you, you big ham?
说起来好笑
It's funny.
小时候  我有着坚定的宗教信仰
As a kid, I was super religious.
我曾是个辅祭[改变]男童
I was an altar boy.
我把长袍的下摆改了下  好秀出我的美腿
I altered the hem of my frock to show off my gams.
我喜欢这个父亲般的角色
I like the idea of this father figure
似乎比我的亲生父亲还要对我感兴趣
that seemed way more interested in me than my real dad.
我曾来这里寻求建议  安慰
I actually turned to this for advice, comfort,
当我开始产生性吸引力时
and when I started having attractions
我来这里寻求帮助
and I looked here for help,
我发现我是被憎恶的一类人
I found out I was an abomination,
这本曾让我觉得不那么孤单的书
and this book that had made me feel less lonely
突然间让我觉得孤单无比
suddenly made me feel completely alone.
是啊  我也有过同样的经历
Yeah, I was there, too,
但上帝可不仅仅是那本书而已
but God is more than just that book.
这一切让我好困惑
It's all so confusing to me.
如此掏心挠肝地想要一个人
I mean, wanting someone so much
却被告知我不该有这样的情感
and then being told I wasn't supposed to want it,
我认识的好多同性恋
and so many gay guys I knew
都通过喝酒或吸毒来埋葬这种情感
just buried those feelings by getting drunk or high.
《利未记》上确实说
Well, Leviticus does say,
"男人和男人上床  就该被处以石刑"
"If a man lies with another man, he should be stoned."
我听着呢
So I'm listening.
你从这里能获得什么启发
What do you get out of this?
每次我来到这里  就会闭上眼睛
Well, I come here, I close my eyes,
然后去想  对我重要的东西
and I think about what matters to me
我感恩的东西
and what I'm grateful for,
然后立刻就能获得一种平静感
and a sense of peace comes over me.
-听上去不错  -试试看
- Sounds nice. - Try it.
现在吗
Now?
好吧  对我重要的...
Okay. What matters to--
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
现在对我来说最重要的  就是保护好我的孩子
What matters to me right now is protecting my child.
我感恩的是
And I'm grateful that
我要将一个孩子带来这世上
I'm bringing this child into the world.
这就对了嘛  是不是觉得...
There you go. Doesn't that feel--
尽管这个世界  冰盖在融化
The world where the ice caps are melting,
蜜蜂在灭绝
bees are dying,
低腰牛仔裤又开始风靡起来
low-rise jeans are coming back,
更别提等我的孩子上大学的时候
not to mention the fact that when my kid is in college,
我都70岁了
I'll be 70,
如果我还有见到孙子孙女的机会
and if I ever get to meet my grandkids,
估计就是我的头被放在罐子里储存着
I'll probably be a head in a jar.
好了  好了
Okay, okay, okay.
一开始还挺积极的
Good first attempt.
对不起  杰克  我...
I'm sorry, Jack. I--
我真希望我有你这样的信仰
I actually wish I could have the faith you have.
威尔  你就要当父亲了
Will, you--you're going to be a father.
那简直是这世上最强大的信仰之跃啊
That's the biggest leap of faith there is.
以及你竟敢在超市买那盒染发剂
That and you buying that box of supermarket hair dye.
我有优惠券嘛
I had a coupon.
并且定时器响的时候我睡过去了  好吗
And I slept through the timer, all right?
会褪掉的  会褪掉的
It'll fade. It'll fade.
但是听着  这个世界永远会有很多
But, look, the world is always gonna be filled
你无法控制的东西
with things you can't control.
那正是来这里的目的
That's what coming here is for--
将那些压力不满等负能量都释放出来
to release that to something outside of you.
不然你觉得我为何长年比你活得轻松自在
Why do you think I'm so much less stressed out than you all the time?
我一直觉得是因为你的一切花销都是我在买单
I always assumed it was because I pay for everything
以及你不用承担任何责任
and you have no responsibilities whatsoever,
但是  我明白你的意思了
but I see your point.
我只是觉得我做不到
I just don't think I can do
放开一切  让上帝做主
the whole let go and let God thing.
那么...
Then...
就放开一切  让我做主
then let go and let me, hmm?
当压力太大的时候
When it all gets to be too much,
把你承受的一些担忧烦恼交给我
just give me some of that worry you're holding onto
让我来帮你背负  好吗
and let me carry it, huh?
让我作为你的教堂
Let me be your church.
我的确很崇拜你
Well, I do worship you.
-谢谢你  杰克  -没事
- Thanks, Jack. - Yeah.
快看啊
Oh, look.
是鸡奸[索多玛]和基傻[蛾摩拉]耶
It's Sodom and Gay Moron.
索多玛和蛾摩拉
是《圣经》里的罪恶之城
糟糕  祂察觉到我来了  快跑
Crap, he knows I'm here. Let's get out of here.
詹姆斯  你来这里干什么
James, what are you doing here?
自然  我被开除了
Well, naturally, I was fired.
不要啊
Oh, no.
你会再找到新工作的  对吧
You'll get another job, right?
毕竟纽约还有很多海洋馆
With all the aquariums in New York?
不  只有那一个
No, there's just the one.
我真的很抱歉
I am so, so sorry.
不  是我该道歉  格蕾丝
No, I'm sorry, Grace.
我生你的气了  但你说得对
I got angry with you, but you were right.
那只是个意外  所以我来是想说...
It was just an accident, so I'm here to say...
我们能重新开始吗
Can we try again?
什么
What?
你是疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
我跟你老子和儿子都上过床
I slept with your son and your father,
但你却原谅了你
and you forgave me.
我在你的公寓拉屎导致屎漫金山
I pooped your apartment to death,
你也原谅了我
and you forgave me.
现在我侵犯了一只海豚  害你被开除了
But now I violated a porpoise, got you fired,
导致一个物种灭绝
and ended a species!
我还是原谅你
And I forgive you.
你是有什么毛病啊
What is wrong with you?
我觉得我爱上你了
I think I'm falling for you.
提升一下你的标准  老兄
Raise your standards, man!
对不起  对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
我无法跟一个看女人眼光这么差劲的人在一起
I can't be with someone who has such terrible tastes in women.